SEAN BLOMMAERT

SENIOR DRUPAL DEVELOPER http://www.seanblommaert.nl

SUMMARY

Sean Patrick Blommaert August 3, 1985 Zoetermeer, Netherlands

T: +316 2462 5019 E: info@seanblommaert.nl An experienced software engineer with a passion for Drupal and Open Source. Acquia Certified backend developer, who loves working on challenging projects with talented people. Analytical problem solver, excels as an intermediary between technology and business. Inspiring team lead and mentor. Active Drupal (core) contributor, key member of the Media Initiative for Drupal 8 core.

SKILLS

Expertise Drupal development / Team lead / Software architecture / System

integration / Security / Training

Soft skills Analytical / Communicative / Flexible / Result-oriented / Team player

CMS Drupal

Programming PHP/SQL/JavaScript/jQuery/HTML5/CSS/SASS

System integration REST / SOAP / SAML2 / Oauth

Apache / Git / SVN / Drush / PHPStorm / JIRA / Apache Solr / Software

Elastic Search / Memcache / Redis / Varnish

Databases MySQL / PostgreSQL / Oracle / Microsoft SQL Server

Operating Systems Mac OS / Ubuntu / Debian / Windows

Dutch (native) / Engels Languages

EXPERIENCE

2013 - present Senior Software Engineer, Finalist

> Lead developer and Drupal architect for a wide range of projects. Involved in the recruitment/hiring process and training/coaching junior/medior developers.

Some examples of developed applications are:

- Utrecht University (uu.nl)
- Maastricht University (maastrichtuniversity.nl)
- Amsterdam Museum (amsterdammuseum.nl)
- Nedap Security (nedapsecurity.com)

Drupal Developer, Total Active Media

Responsible for technical design, implementation and maintenance of a wide range of Drupal applications.

Some examples of developed applications are:

- Sound and Vision Institute (beeldengeluid.nl)
- ConQuaestor (financeincorporated.nl and conquaestor.nl)
- National Maritime Museum (hetscheepvaartmuseum.nl)
- ROC Midden Nederland (rocmn.nl)

2008 - 2013

2006 - 2008	Jr. SAP consultant, Nuon ICT
-------------	------------------------------

Responsible for architecture, configuration and maintenance of multiple SAP

Enterprise environments.

2004 - 2006 Coldfusion developer, Zappwerk (internship)

University

Involved in the design and implementation of several high profile websites.

Some examples of developed applications are:

- Intertoys (intertoys.nl)
- Dutchs Museum Association (museum.nl)
- Utrecht University (uu.nl)

• Cultuurnet Vlaanderen, Flemish government (cultuurnet.be)

EDUCATION

2017	Acquia Certified Developer - Back end Specialist (D8)
2016	Acquia Certified Developer - Back end Specialist (D7)
2014	Acquia Certified Developer (D7)
2007	Technical Consultant SAP Netweaver '04 - SAP Web AS for Oracle, SAP Netherlands
2002 - 2006	Bachelor of Information and Communication Technology, The Hague